Indiana University Folklore Institute Material Culture papers, 1953-1984, bulk 1960-1981 C614
Indiana University Archives
- Student Papers (Box 1)
  - M/C 71/7 Owens, Steven G. No Title (Eline Galloway - furniture repairer, North America, U.S., Indiana - Furniture Repairer), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, October 26, 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 71/8 Miller, James C. "Folklore 721 - Field Project" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilt Making & Society), F721, Instructor Unknown, August 10, 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 71/9 Warner, Kathleen. "The Sammy Bartlett House" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, House), F720, Dr. Roberts, July 9, 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 71/10 Meekins, John. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, Log Houses), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 71/11 Cebulski, Marcia. "Bread A Foodways Exploration" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Food, Bread), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Spring 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 71/12 Meekins, John. "Eight Log Houses In the Polk Township Area" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, House, Log Cabin), Class # Unknown, Dr. Warren Roberts, June 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/1 Sams, Robert W. "Margret Morse an Oral Life History" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F810, Dr. Roberts, August 18, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/2 Hollenbeck, Joanne. "Folklore of Indiana the Preston Home in Terre Haute" (Richard Van Allen – Manager of the Terre Haute Realty Corporation and Terre Haute House Hotel, North America, U.S., Indiana – House History), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/3 Brandon, Jamie. "Quilting a Traditional Craft" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilting), F220, Coelho, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/4 Padgett, Emilie. "Folklore 101" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Food Cupboards), F101, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/5 Smith, Debra Kay. "Meal Habits of the American Family" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Meal Habits), F101, Jo Lombardo, December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/6 Gearhart, Fayette Ann. "Recipes" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Recipe, Sugared, Popcorn), F391, William E. Lightfoot, Fall 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/7 Pottorff, Cynthia. "Rug Braiding" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Rug Braiding), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/8 Robinson, Steven. "Folklore 101 – Project" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Weaving), F101, Instructor Unknown, November 29, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/9 Gates, Deb. "Folklore for Bill Lightfoot" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Rugs, Loom, & Rags), F391, Bill Lightfoot, Fall 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/10 DeVoe, Don. "The Craft of Quilt-Making" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 29, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/11 Keel, Doris. "Quiltmaking" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F101, Instructor Unknown, November 29, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/12 Henderson, Karen. "The Art of Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F101, Instructor Unknown, November 29, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/14 Melloncamp, Sandra. "Folk Recipes" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Recipes), F391, Mr. Bill Lightfoot, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/13 Jones, Barbara. "The Craft of Making Moonshine in West Virginia" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Still & Distill Moonshine), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/15 Browning, Cathy. "Quilting: its Functions in Society and Why it is Dying 'to bee or not to bee…'" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F220, Lewis, December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/16 Meyer, Curtis A. "(Elizabeth Wergler [?] Smedley, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F391, Mr. William Lightfoot, November 27, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/17 Trotter, Rosemary A. "Indiana Folklore Project on Quilts and Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/18 Fountain, Madge M. "Pieced Quilt Patterns" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), Indiana Folklore, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C Riggs, Alan L. "A Folk and her Quilted Life or the Mis-guided Folklorist" (Mrs. Chris 'Minny' Merta – Housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilting Story), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 20-23, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/20 Mesnick, Donna Sue. "The Quilt Making of Mrs. Ruble Bays" (Mrs. Ruble Bays – retired Civil Service worker, North America, U.S., Indiana, Madison County, Anderson – Quilts), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/21 Lahrman, Helen C. "Epitaphs, Engravings, and Inscriptions on tombstones in Jackson County" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombes & Epitaphs), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/22 Grant, Douglas L. "Folklore Seat Weaving" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Furniture, Seat Weaving), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 27, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/23 Walton, Lucinda. "Pennsylvania German Hex Signs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Hex Signs, German), F220, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/24 Cleaveland, Bob. "Candlemaking" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Candle Making), F101, Instructor Unknown, November 28, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/25 Hennessy, Lynn. "Angel Site" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Indian), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 6, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/26 Lutes, Nanette. "Lost Crafts Dying and Revitalized" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Chari Caning & Metal Plating), F101, Mr. Adams, December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/27 Kimmerli, Dale. "The Russel House and Elements which Influenced its Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, House), F101, John U. Lach (?), April 28, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/28 Considine, Sue. "Ojibwa Basketry" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Basketry, Ojibwa), F220, Mr. Byrd, April 21, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/29 Goodrich, Beverly. "Butchering, Haymaking, Threshing" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Butchering & Haying), F391, Professor William E. Lightfoot, November 27, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/30 Etchison, Paula. "Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Epitaphs), F101, Denby (T.A.), April 27, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/31 Kaufman, Jane. "The Folklore Craft of Butchering" (Lucille Hackman - clerk/buyer and housewife, North America, U.S., Indiana - Butchering), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/32 West, Rhea Bessie. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tombstones), Indiana Folklore, Lightfoot, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/33 Kocher, Mike. "Blacksmithing as Folklore" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Blacksmithing), F101, Coelho, November 29, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/34 Rueff, Donna Jean. "The Story of the Old Smokehouse" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Smokehouse), F391, Mr. Bill Lightfoot, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/35 Zahrn, Will. "A Study of Weather Vanes in Bloomington, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Weather Vanes - Craft), F101, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/36 Shadel, Marty. "A comparison of Tombstones from a Northern Illinois Cemetery with those of two Southern Indiana Cemeteries" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Illinois - Tombstone Comparison), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/39 Spurgeon, Carol. "The Pride of Providence: An Insight into the Historic Material Culture of Early Johnson County Residents" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tools, Misc., History of Johnson County), Class # Unknown, William Lightfoot, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/40 Hey, Nancy. "Building Log Cabins" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Log Cabins), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/41 Tryon, Mary Mae. "Butchering" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Butchering), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/42 Greskovich, James. "Kentucky, the Melting Pot of America Folk Crafts" (North America, U.S., Kentucky - Craft, General), F101, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/43 Carper, Sue A. "Folklore Project" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tombstones & Epitaphs), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/44 Kash, Graham S. "Country-Church Architecture in Green County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Green County - Architecture, Church), Material Culture, Dr. Roberts, December 13, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/45 Feaser, Timothy P. "Historical & descriptive Survey of a Southern Georgian House" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, House, Georgian), F220, Instructor Unknown, December 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/46 Viernes-Enriquez, Mrs. Joy. "Philippine Architecture: Pre-Spanish to the Present" (East Asia, Philippines - Architecture, Historical), F720, Dr. Warren Roberts, December 14, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/47 Gater, Val. "Round Barns" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Barns, Round), F101, Miss Jo Lombardi, November 28, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/48 Small, Alan. "Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Epitaphs), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/49 Cullen, Susan. "Tombstone Inscriptions" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tombstones), Class # Unknown, Mr. Lightfoot, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/50 Deppert, James Leslie. "The Barn on Greencastle Road" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Barn), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/51 Clement, Becky. "Project" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County - Quilts), F220, P. Denby (T.A.), December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/52 Conley, Ronald. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Town), F220, Phillip George, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/53 Vaught, Kevin. "Fence Building" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Fence Building), F391, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/54 Lombardo, Josephine. "A Look at Contemporary Quilting in Southern Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilting, Southern Indiana, Contemporary), Indiana Folklore, Dr. Warren Roberts (submitted August 19, 1972)., Fall 1971 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/55 Lund, Jens. "The Walls Log Barn, Monroe County, Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, Barn), F720, Instructor Unknown, December 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/56 Gilmore, Janet. "The Prather Road Log House Bean Blossom Township Monroe County Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Architecture, House, Log), F720, Dr. Warren E. Roberts, December 1, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 72/57 Small, Vicki. "Quilt Patterns" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilting Patterns), F391, Instructor Unknown, August 7, 1972 (Box 3)
  - M/C 73/1 Decker, T.R. "John Fischer – Blacksmith" (North America, U.S., Indiana), F101, Miss Lombardo, Spring 1973 (Box 3)
  - M/C 73/2 Begley, Phyllis. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food Prep, Corn, Dry), F391, Lightfoot, September 23, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/3 Rothgeb, Jeanne. "Some Food Traditions of a German American Family" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food, German, Tradition), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/4 Wertz, Susan. "The Folklore of Canning" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food Preservation, Canning), F391, Instructor Unknown, April 5, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/5 Rettig, Raymond. "Folk-Methods of Canning Fruit and Sealing Fruit Jars" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food Preservation, Canning), F391, Lightfoot, November 9, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/6 Chauvette, Christine. "French Canadian Recipes" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Recipes), F220, Jens Lund (T.A.), Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/7 Scott, Melinda. "Food - German Cheese and Cottage Cheese" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Food, Cottage Cheese), F101, William Lightfoot, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C Sikora, Susan. "Pirohi" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Recipes, Croatian), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/9 Champlin, Marti. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft Too, Cookie Cutter), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 27, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/10 Skeen, Patricia. "A Natural Sweet[e]ner" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Maple Sugar Production), Class # Unknown, Glassie/Marshall, April 25, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/11 Beitman, James A. "An Interview with Mr. Roberts, a Sorghum Miller" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Brown County, Gnawbone), F220, Dr. Glassie, Jens Lund (T.A.), November 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/12 Lee, Catherine. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Food, Recipes, Animal), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/13 Toogood, Tilly. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts, Designs), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, November 6, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/14 Sartoris, Donna Kay. "Quilting Social" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilting, Social), Indiana Folklore, Mr. Lightfoot, June 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/15 Winchester, Tim. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Bill Lightfoot, April 27, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/16 Stephens, Dorothy L. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F391, Lightfoot, Jun. 14, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/17 Fannin, Linda. "Quilts" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Instructor Unknown, November 29, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/18 Stickles, Nancy. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, October 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/19 Gafken, Melanie. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, December 18, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/20 Reynolds, Sherry. "The Art of Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/21 Wachob, Carol. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/22 Thomas, Shirley Kay. "Quilts, Quilt Making, and Quilt Patterns" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts, Designs), F391, Lightfoot, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/23 Littlejohn, Robin. "Quilting: Yesterday and Today" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 11, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/24 Juroff, Jane K. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/25 Bevers, Candance Ann. "Tatting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tatting, Recipes), F391, Instructor Unknown, April 5, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/26 Marciniak, Marianne. "A Vanishing Art" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Textile, Polish), F220, Dennis Coelho, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/27 Koepp, Michael. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Rug, Hooked), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/28 Champlin, Marty. "Material Folk Art" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Rug, Rag), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 4, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/29 Carter, Pam. "Folk Crafts Assignment #1" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Weaving, Bedspread), F101, Instructor Unknown, April 13, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/30 Agan, Brenda. "Quilting in Southern Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Mr. Bill McNeil, August 14, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/31 Buffalo, Marc. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F101, J.O. Lombardo, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/32 Stickles, Nancy. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F391, Mr. Lightfoot, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/33 Tillman, Nancy. "Quilting: A Folkcraft" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Instructor Unknown, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/34 Stark, Peggy Stahl. "The Folkart of Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F391, Lightfoot, June 14, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/35 Foxworthy, Kathy. "Quilting" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts), F220, Coelho, May 1, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/36 Allen, Cynthia. "Collection Project on Quilt Patterns and Quilting Parties" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Quilts, Parties), Class # Unknown, Mr. Lightfoot, June 13, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/37 McWhirter, Bridgette Zahnle. "Lawnmowers and a Changing Society: a grave situation" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Tombstones, History), F220, Rusty Marshall, April 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/38 Foster, Marjorie G. "Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Epitaphs), F391, Mr. William E. Lightfoot, November 6, 1973 (Box 4)
  - MC 73/39 Madden, Jan. "Stoneware John Mills, Potter" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Potter, Stoneware), F220, Lightfoot, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/40 Wilkerson, Keith. No Title (John Mills – potter, North America, U.S., Indiana - Pottery Making), F220, Yens Lund (?), December 7, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/41 Pomatto, Claudia. "Basketry as a Tradition" (William Bohall - basket weaver, North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Basketry), F220, Bill McNeil, December 18 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/42 Kemp, Jeri. "The Lost Art of Cabinet-Making Mac Molden, Cabinet Maker" (North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Cabinet-Making), F220, Jens Lund (T.A.), November 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/43 Morgan, Margaret. No Title (Reuben Morgan – basket making, North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Basket-Making), F391, Instructor Unknown, October 31, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/44 Clark, Cynthia. No Title (Howard Bruce Hovis - handyman/basket weaver, North America, U.S., Indiana - Craft, Basket-Making), F391, Lightfoot, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/45 Snider, Brian. "Indian Silverwork" (Larry Spicer – jewelry collector, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Silverwork, Indian), F220, McNeil, December 11, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/46 Weaver, Joe. "Some Gravestone Motifs in Northwester Illinois" (North America, U.S., Indiana, ILL – Tombstones, Motifs), F220, Lightfoot, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/47 Inglert, Jeannenne. "The Art of Primitive Candle Dipping" (Susan Feller – candle maker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Candle Dipping), F391(?), Lightfoot, June 13, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/48 Weinheimer, Greg. "Chair Caning" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Chair Caning), F220, Dennis Coelho, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/49 Jackson, Cinda. "Basketry" (Anna Overdorf – basket making, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Basketry), F391, Lightfoot, Summer 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/50 Walstrum, Sarah. "String Figures" (Gina Marshall – making of string figures, North America, U.S., Indiana – String Figures), F220, McNeil, December 18, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/51 Barnett, Stephen. No Title (Mrs. Lawetta Marjorie Jacobs – ceramics, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Ceramics), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, March 31, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/52 Sprague, Jim. "The Country Auction and the Auctioneer" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Auctioneering), F220, Coelho, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/53 Rupe, Mary Ellen. "Tombstone Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones & Epitaphs), F391, William Lightfoot, Summer 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/54 Weishaar, Larry. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 19, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/55 Clark, Richard. No Title (Mrs. Hester Matthews Alley Porter, North America, U.S., Indiana – Cemetery, Family, Tombstones), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, March 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/56 Maynard, Merry. "Easter Foods among the Russian Orthodox in Bloomington Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Food, Easter, Russian Orthodox), F712, Dr. Roberts, April 30, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/57 Ohrn, Steven. "The Lumbras" (North America, U.S., Indiana, - Craft, Wood carving), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/58 Hoffman, Doris. "Epitaphs" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Epitaphs), F391, William E. Lightfoot, First Summer Term 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/59 Lundy, Marcia K. "You Can't Take It With You: Tombstone Epitaphiania" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstone Epitaphs), Class # Unknown, Phil George, May 3, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/60 Pennington, Jerry. "Pennsylvania Dutch 'Hex Signs'" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Hex Signs, Pennsylvania Dutch), F220, Dennis Coelho, March 27, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/61 Irvine, Robert and Constance. "Geanell Carmen" (Geanell Carmen – folk art painter, North America, U.S., Indiana – Art, Painting, Drawing), F220, Wm. McNeil, 2nd Summer Session 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 72/62 Hall Kathryn. "Gravestones of Southern Indiana 1840-1890" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 18, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/63 Foley Jr., William R. "Project Tucker" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Occupation, Auto Mechanic), F220, Glassie, Fall 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/64 Frisz, Joe. ""A Case Study of the Folklore of Fishing in Indiana" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Sport, Fishing, Place and Equipment), Dennis Coelho, April 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/65 Berry, Marge. "The Belle of Louisville" (North America, U.S., Kentucky – Occupational Lore, Paddle-Boatmen, Steam), F220, Instructor Unknown, April 16, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/66 Head, William (Bill). "Quarry Work in the 1920's A Dialogue with Rufus Head" (Rufus Head – retired stone worker, North America, U.S., Indiana – Occupation, Quarry work), F220, Professor Glassie, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/67 George, Eric. "The Stone Quarrying Operation; Jobs and Techniques Day in the Life of a Waterboy" (Richard Lake – dispatcher with moving company, Floyd Vibbart – quarryman, North America, U.S., Indiana – Occupation, Quarry work, Waterboy), F220, Dennis Coelho, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/68 Baffaloe, Marc. "Folk Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Monroe County, Polk Township), F101, J.O. Lombardo, Spring 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/69 Wicks, Benedicte. "The German Barn" (North America, U.S., Indiana, St. Joseph County, Walkerton), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, April 23, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/70 Ryder, Joyce. "Ole Steffen Dahl: the Violin Maker" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Violin Making), F220, Dennis Coelho, May 3, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/71 Niswander, Sarah. "Folklore Project Tomb Stones" (North America, U.S., Indiana, Virginia, Washington D.C. – Tombstones), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/72 Wood, Jim. No Title (Jessie Jewel Wood – housewife, North America, U.S., Northern Arkansas – Farm Customs), F220, Glassie, November 3, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/73 Kincaid, Michael W. "Grandma & Granddaddy's House" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, House, Farm), F101, Jo Lombardo, April 27, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/74 Dumford, Peggy. No Title (North America, U.S., Indiana – Architecture, House), Class # Unknown, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/75 Wilkerson, Gwendolyn. "Threshing Day of the Past" (Carl Runge – farmer, North America, U.S., Indiana – Occupation, Farm, Thresh), Class # Unknown, William E. Lightfoot, March 11, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/76 Muhammad, Bala. "Traditional Farming and House Building in Northern Nigeria" (Africa, Nigeria, Northern – Architecture, House Building), F721, Professor W. Roberts, Second Semester 1972/73 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/77 Jacobs, Morris A. "Limestone Carving: A Dying Art" (Frank A. Arena – retired limestone carver, North America, U.S., Indiana – Craft, Limestone Carving), F220, Henry Glassie, December 7, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/78 Viernes-Enriquez, Joy. "The Traditional Craftsman among the Filipino People" (Asia, Philippines – Craftsmen), F721, Dr. Warren Roberts, May 2, 1973 (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/79 Morris, Ann. "Material Folklore: Gravestone Architecture" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Tombstones), F220, Marshall (TA?) (Professor Glassie?), Date Unknown (Box 4)
  - M/C 73/80 Stanley, Wanda L. "Mooresville Cultural Contribution Quilts and Recipes" (North America, U.S., Indiana – Quilts), F391, Instructor Unknown, Date Unknown (Box 4)